{
    "id": "f78f94c307c3487bb6e74d37dc2d3706",
    "title": "Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "His ………………… led to his fall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "proud",
                "pride"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We are waiting for the …………………. of the news.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "confirm",
                "conform",
                "confirmation"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Failure is the stepping stone to …………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "success",
                "succession"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is an ……………….  young man driven by his desire to change the world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ambition",
                "ambiguous",
                "ambitious"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "One should be satisfied with one’s …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "accomply",
                "accomplish",
                "accomplishments"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "His ………………….. to learn English helped him in his later life.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "determine",
                "determination",
                "determinant"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If you follow my advice, you will ……………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "success",
                "successful",
                "succeed"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "His father has given him his …………………. to go abroad.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "permit",
                "permission",
                "permissible"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "His ……………….. is contagious.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enthuse",
                "enthusiasm",
                "enthusiastic"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is very ………………… about his new project.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enthuse",
                "enthusiastic",
                "enthusiasm"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}